# Sergey Gromkov

### Frontend developer



10 years in frontend development. Before switching to Yandex Market I developed the interface of a large high-load sports-themed website. Before that I made about 40 websites from the beginning to the release stage working in a web studio.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Yandex,** Software Engineering Frontend developer

DEC 2021 - PRESENT | Moscow, Russia

Develop the client side of Yandex Market:

- Develop user interfaces and client logic;
- Implement unit and e2e-tests;

### **Uma.Tech**, Software Engineering Frontend Team Lead

DEC 2016 - DEC 2021 | Moscow, Russia

Develop the client side of matchtv.ru:

- Design the architecture and responsible for choosing the technical stack;
- Develop user interfaces and client logic;
- Implement unit tests;
- Write documentation and development agreements;
- Write text and video guides for testing complex interfaces and advertising on the site.

### **Rocket Studio**, Web Studio *Web developer*

SEN 2011 - FEB 2015 | Moscow, Russia

Developing websites using Bitrix Framework.

#### **EDUCATION**

Moscow State Technological University "STANKIN" Bachelor's degree in Software development



#### **CONTACTS**

telegram: @sgromkov

sgromkov@gmail.com

Moscow, Russia

#### **SKILLS**

**Javascript** 

Typescript

React

Redux

MobX

Webpack

**Jest** 

Hermione

HTML

CSS

MongoDB

Docker

Git

#### LINKS

linkedin.com/in/sgromkov

github.com/sgromkov

gromkov.me

#### **LANGUAGES**

Russian - native

English - Intermediate